现在我们来一个终极测试层次 这是一个非常严肃  而且
Now for the big quiz. In all seriousness, this is the most
很复杂的测试  需要用到你所学的所有知识  你要做的就是
complicated exercise I've given you so far this lesson. I want you
去使用cusor loader和multiple text view去完成details view
to implement the details view using the cursor loader and multiple text view
我已经给你很多的线索啦  请使用loaders
widgets. And I've got some hints for you. Use loaders
而不是adapters  这意味着什么  呵呵  这意味着你的detail
not adapters. What does this mean? Well, it makes sense. Your detail
view不能包含一个列表  你不需要去
view does not contain a list so you don't
使用一个adapter  不过你依然需要使用
need to use an adapter, but you can still
一个loader pattern  这个loader pattern将会自动的
use the loader pattern. The loader pattern will automatically
观察所有在URI里Cursorloader的变化
observe for changes in the URI with a CursorLoader. The
第二  你需要做的是输入你想要
second thing you want to do is pass the date
的日期  这个日期将会是一个非常重要的
into your intent. The date is the important thing to
细节数据当你需要输入的时候会提供
the detail you need to have passed into it
一个content provider的查询  好的  现在你要记住  你可以
to properly query the content provider. Now remember, you can
从utility函数中拿到现在的位置设置  这就是
actually get the current location settings from the utility function. So
你全部所需要的数据  我希望这些线索能帮到你
all you really need is the date. I hope that helps.